seotechnocrat.com 2014-06-11

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy policy of our user is very important for us. Now here we will tell you which type of information we collect from the visitors and how we use it?

The Privacy policy of [www.seotechnocrat.com](http://www.seotechnocrat.com/) is revised from time to time now it’s your duty to check with the passage of time. We also mention the last updated date of this document at the end of the page.

Please read the privacy policy of [www.seotechnocrat.com](http://www.seotechnocrat.com/) before using this website if you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this website so we are requesting from you that not to use this website.

First of all I want to say that any information we collect from our user’s, aren’t disclosed to the third party because we know that your information is personally identifiable. We collect information when you subscribe our newsletter for this you have to fill your full name and email address but this information are kept as a secret and not disclosed in any circumstances.

**Do we use Log Files?**

And the answer is yes, like other website on the web we also use Log files which contains the information about the user. The information is stored in the log files are your internet protocol address that is also known as an IP address and your ISP that is an Internet Service Provider and We also track the number of pages visited by the user etc. All these information are collected by us but we don’t share any information with others.

**Do we use Cookies and Web Beacons?**

Yeah, we use cookies to store information about a particular user. Cookies are a very small text files which are stored on your hard drive and this file is not used to transfer any suspicious program or virus to your computer. The cookies are very important because it tells us a page is visited by a specific user it also gives the content related information, and we promise to our visitors that we don’t disclose in a public.

**Contact us**

If you have any doubt this privacy policy document then feel free to ask anything from us. We will get back to you as soon as possible.

**E-mail**  : info@seotechnocrat.com[](mailto:basicpctipsofficial@gmail.com)

Or you can use your contact us page.

This document is last updated on 8th Oct, 2013.

**NOTE : Your IP (Internet Protocol) address and your Location is never shared with the Third Party in any circumstances.**
